[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who determined the order in which the astrological signs appear?", "correct_answer": "Buddha", "incorrect_answers": ["Christ", "Osiris", "Zeus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What shape does the rice in the traditional Indonesian dish Tumpeng have?", "correct_answer": "Cone", "incorrect_answers": ["Fish", "Ball", "Sun"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who provided the voices of the characters in the Radio Program Amos n Andy from 1928 to 1960?", "correct_answer": "Freeman Gosden and Charles Correll", "incorrect_answers": ["Pranklin Pierce and John Pierce", "Amos Rogers and Andrew Brown", "John Paul and George Ringo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What company bought Opel in 1931?", "correct_answer": "General Motors", "incorrect_answers": ["FIAT", "Darracq S.A.", "Chrysler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following statements is wrong?", "correct_answer": "There are seven living species of sloths.", "incorrect_answers": ["Two-toed sloths have only six cervical vertebrae instead of seven.", "Sloths hairs grow away from their extremities instead of towards them.", "Three-toed sloths have nine cervical vertebrae instead of seven."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the title of the national anthem of Madagascar, written by Norbert Raharisoa and composed by Rahajason?", "correct_answer": "Oh, Our Beloved Fatherland", "incorrect_answers": ["Dear Motherland", "Blessed Island", "Rise, Oh, Rise"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Upon hearing my screams, my husband stepped out of the shower to make sure I was alright, causing me recoil due to my gymnophobia. What was I afraid of?", "correct_answer": "Nudity", "incorrect_answers": ["Men", "Getting wet", "Water"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this game, you make melds of 3 or more cards. You can go out with 10 points or less. If your opponent undercuts you, you lose the difference in your points.", "correct_answer": "Gin Rummy", "incorrect_answers": ["Pinochle", "Pitch", "42"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the enzyme bromelain that is present in pineapples?", "correct_answer": "It breaks down protein.", "incorrect_answers": ["Its content increases with the coking or canning of the fruit.", "It speeds up the action of gelatin.", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The active ingredient of absinthe is thujone. It is chemically similar to this psychoactive substance. Scientists also believe that thujone and this substance affect the same brain receptors.", "correct_answer": "Tetrahydrocannabinol", "incorrect_answers": ["Beta-phenylethylamine", "Opium", "Codeine Phosphate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the Louisiana Museum of Modern Art?", "correct_answer": "Denmark", "incorrect_answers": ["New Orleans, Louisiana", "Batob Rouge, Louisiana", "Shreveport , Louisiana"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it true that the role of Superman was Christopher Reeves first movie role?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}]